[
  {
    "question": "An artificial barrier made from improvised materials, used during uprisings",
    "answer": "BARRICADE"
  },
  {
    "question": "An official organization in the Roman Catholic Church whose purpose was to find and punish people who opposed its beliefs",
    "answer": "INQUISITION"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cutting of or operation on a living animal usually for physiological or pathological investigation.",
    "answer": "VIVISECTION"
  },
  {
    "question": "A strong, regular repeated pattern of movement or sound.",
    "answer": "RHYTHM"
  },
  {
    "question": "A continuous moving strip or surface that is used for transporting objects from one place to another",
    "answer": "CONVEYOR"
  },
  {
    "question": "To speak very quietly, using the breath but not the voice",
    "answer": "WHISPER"
  },
  {
    "question": "A set of mathematical instructions or rules that, especially if given to a computer, will help to calculate an answer to a problem:",
    "answer": "ALGORITHM"
  },
  {
    "question": "The quality of existing as or representing an idea, a feeling, etc. and not a material object, or something that has this quality",
    "answer": "ABSTRACTION"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ability of different objects to be accessed through the same interface, allowing a single function or method to operate on different types in a unified way",
    "answer": "POLYMORPHISM"
  },
  {
    "question": "The giving out of light by a substance that has not been heated",
    "answer": "LUMINESCENCE"
  }
]
